<en-US>
E-reader optimization is now manual-only inside editor tools. Settings toggle was removed, and source labels were refined across locales.
</en-US>
<ar>
Tahsin e-reader asbaha yadawi faqat dakhil adawat al-muharrir. Tam izalat mubaddil al-iadadat, wa tahsin nusus al-masdar fi jami al-lughat.
</ar>
<de-DE>
Die e-reader Optimierung ist jetzt nur noch manuell in den Editor Werkzeugen aktiv. Der Schalter in den Einstellungen wurde entfernt und die Quellenlabels wurden in allen Sprachen verbessert.
</de-DE>
<es-419>
La optimizacion para e-reader ahora es solo manual dentro de herramientas del editor. Se elimino el toggle en ajustes y se mejoraron textos de origen en todos los idiomas.
</es-419>
<fr-FR>
L optimisation e-reader est maintenant uniquement manuelle dans les outils de l editeur. Le commutateur des reglages a ete retire et les libelles source ont ete ameliores dans toutes les langues.
</fr-FR>
<hi-IN>
E-reader optimization ab sirf manual hai aur editor tools ke andar milti hai. Settings toggle hata diya gaya hai, aur source labels sabhi bhashaon mein sudhare gaye hain.
</hi-IN>
<it-IT>
L ottimizzazione e-reader ora e solo manuale negli strumenti editor. Il toggle nelle impostazioni e stato rimosso e le etichette sorgente sono state migliorate in tutte le lingue.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
E-reader saitekika wa editor tsuru nai no manual nomi ni henkou. Settings toggle wa sakujo sare, source labels wa subete no locales de kaizen sareta.
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
E-reader choejeokhwa neun ije editor tools aneseo su-dongman sayong doemnida. Settings toggle eun jegeo doeeotgo, source labels neun modeun locale eseo gaeseon doeeotseumnida.
</ko-KR>
<pt-BR>
A otimizacao para e-reader agora e apenas manual nas ferramentas do editor. O toggle de configuracoes foi removido e os textos de origem foram melhorados em todos os idiomas.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
Optimizatsiya dlya e-reader teper tolko ruchnaya v instrumentakh redaktora. Toggle v nastroikakh udalen, a podpisi istochnika uluchsheny vo vsekh lokalakh.
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
E-reader youhua xianzai jin zai editor tools zhong shoudong qiyong. Settings toggle yi yichu, source labels yi zai suoyou locales zhong gaijin.
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
E-reader youhua xianzai jin zai editor tools zhong shoudong qiyong. Settings toggle yi yichu, source labels yi zai suoyou locales zhong gaijin.
</zh-TW>
