<en-US>
Added Image | Scratch source actions. Scratch opens editor directly on background tools. PDF detected crop now matches editor and export output, so preview and final file stay aligned.
</en-US>

<ar>
Tam idafat image | scratch. yabhath scratch al-muharrir mubasharatan ila adawat al-khalfiyah. qass PDF al-mukhtashaf alaan yutabiq muaynat al-muharrir wa natijit al-tasdir.
</ar>

<de-DE>
Image | Scratch Quelle hinzugefuegt. Scratch oeffnet den Editor direkt bei den Hintergrund-Werkzeugen. Erkanntes PDF-Crop stimmt jetzt mit Editor und Export ueberein, damit Vorschau und Ergebnis gleich bleiben.
</de-DE>

<es-419>
Se agregaron acciones de fuente Image | Scratch. Scratch abre el editor directo en herramientas de fondo. El crop detectado del PDF ahora coincide con editor y exportacion, por lo que preview y archivo final quedan alineados.
</es-419>

<fr-FR>
Ajout des actions source Image | Scratch. Scratch ouvre l editeur directement sur les outils de fond. Le crop detecte du PDF correspond maintenant a l editeur et a l export, pour garder preview et resultat alignes.
</fr-FR>

<hi-IN>
Image | Scratch source actions add hue. Scratch editor ko seedha background tools par kholta hai. PDF detected crop ab editor aur export ke saath match karta hai, isliye preview aur final file aligned rehte hain.
</hi-IN>

<it-IT>
Aggiunte azioni sorgente Image | Scratch. Scratch apre l editor direttamente sugli strumenti di sfondo. Il crop PDF rilevato ora coincide con editor ed export, cosi anteprima e file finale restano allineati.
</it-IT>

<ja-JP>
Image | Scratch source action o tsuika. Scratch wa haikei tool ni chokusetu hairu editor de hirakimasu. PDF de kenshutsu sareta crop wa ima editor to export to icchi shi, preview to saishuu file ga zuremasen.
</ja-JP>

<ko-KR>
Image | Scratch source action-i chuga doeeotseumnida. Scratch-neun baegyeong tool-eseo jeuksi editor-reul yeoreumnida. PDF gamji crop-eun ije editor-wa export-gwa ilchihae preview-wa gyeolgwa file-i matseumnida.
</ko-KR>

<pt-BR>
Foram adicionadas acoes de origem Image | Scratch. Scratch abre o editor direto nas ferramentas de fundo. O crop detectado do PDF agora coincide com editor e exportacao, mantendo preview e arquivo final alinhados.
</pt-BR>

<ru-RU>
Dobavleny deistviya istochnika Image | Scratch. Rezhim scratch otkryvaet redaktor srazu na instrumentakh fona. Obnaruzhennyi PDF crop teper sovpadaet s editorom i exportom, poetomu preview i finalnyi fail soglasovany.
</ru-RU>

<zh-CN>
Yi zengjia Image | Scratch laiyuan anniu. Scratch hui zhijie dakaibianjiqi de beijing gongju. PDF zidong jiance de crop xianzai yu editor he export baochi yizhi, preview he zuizhong wenjian bu zai cuowei.
</zh-CN>

<zh-TW>
Yi zengjia Image | Scratch laiyuan anniu. Scratch hui zhijie dakaibianjiqi de beijing gongju. PDF zidong jiance de crop xianzai yu editor he export baochi yizhi, preview he zuizhong wenjian bu zai cuowei.
</zh-TW>
