<en-US>
PDF Cover Maker now uses a more stable native PDF picker path on Android and improves PDF rendering reliability. Recommended apps also show the correct EPUB Cover Changer icon.
</en-US>

<ar>
PDF Cover Maker yastakhdim alan masar ikhtiyar PDF asli akthar istiqraran ala Android wa yuhassin istikrar muaynat PDF. kama yuhir qism altatbiqat almuwassa biha ayqonat EPUB Cover Changer alssahiha.
</ar>

<de-DE>
PDF Cover Maker nutzt jetzt einen stabileren nativen PDF-Picker-Pfad auf Android und verbessert die Zuverlaessigkeit beim PDF-Rendering. In den empfohlenen Apps wird jetzt auch das korrekte EPUB Cover Changer Symbol angezeigt.
</de-DE>

<es-419>
PDF Cover Maker ahora usa una ruta nativa de seleccion de PDF mas estable en Android y mejora la confiabilidad del render de PDF. En apps recomendadas tambien se muestra el icono correcto de EPUB Cover Changer.
</es-419>

<fr-FR>
PDF Cover Maker utilise maintenant un chemin natif de selection PDF plus stable sur Android et ameliore la fiabilite du rendu PDF. Les applications recommandees affichent aussi la bonne icone EPUB Cover Changer.
</fr-FR>

<hi-IN>
PDF Cover Maker ab Android par zyada stable native PDF picker path use karta hai aur PDF rendering reliability ko improve karta hai. Recommended apps mein ab EPUB Cover Changer ka sahi icon dikh raha hai.
</hi-IN>

<it-IT>
PDF Cover Maker ora usa un percorso nativo di selezione PDF piu stabile su Android e migliora l affidabilita del rendering PDF. Nelle app consigliate viene mostrata anche l icona corretta di EPUB Cover Changer.
</it-IT>

<ja-JP>
PDF Cover Maker wa Android de yori antei shita native PDF picker keiro o shiyou shi, PDF ringa no shinraisei mo kaizen. Osusume apuri de EPUB Cover Changer no tadashii aikon mo hyouji sareru.
</ja-JP>

<ko-KR>
PDF Cover Maker-neun Android-eseo deo anjeongjeogin native PDF picker gyeongroreul sayonghago PDF rendering sinroe-seongeul gaeseonhaetseumnida. Recommended apps-eseo EPUB Cover Changer ui ollbareun aikon-do pyosi doemnida.
</ko-KR>

<pt-BR>
O PDF Cover Maker agora usa um caminho nativo de selecao de PDF mais estavel no Android e melhora a confiabilidade do rendering de PDF. Os apps recomendados tambem exibem o icone correto do EPUB Cover Changer.
</pt-BR>

<ru-RU>
PDF Cover Maker teper ispolzuet bolee stabilnyi native put vybora PDF na Android i uluchshaet nadezhnost renderinga PDF. V rekomenduemykh prilozheniyakh takzhe pokazyvaetsya pravilnaya ikonka EPUB Cover Changer.
</ru-RU>

<zh-CN>
PDF Cover Maker xianzai zai Android shang shiyong geng wending de yuansheng PDF xuanze lujing, bing tisheng le PDF xuanran de kekaoxing. Tuijian yingyong ye hui xianshi zhengque de EPUB Cover Changer tubiao.
</zh-CN>

<zh-TW>
PDF Cover Maker xianzai zai Android shang shiyong geng wending de yuansheng PDF xuanze lujing, bing tisheng le PDF xuanzan de kekaoxing. Tuijian yingyong ye hui xianshi zhengque de EPUB Cover Changer tubiao.
</zh-TW>
