<en-US>
Fallback export flow is now more reliable when rewarded ads fail, with better tour coordination and trial consumption only after successful output.
</en-US>
<ar>
Tatbiq masar fallback lil tasdir asbaha akthar istiqraran inda fashal iilan rewarded, maa tansiq afdal maa al-tour wa istihlak al-try baad natijah najihah faqat.
</ar>
<de-DE>
Der Fallback Export Ablauf ist jetzt zuverlaessiger bei Rewarded Ad Fehlern, mit besserer Tour Abstimmung und Verbrauch des Testexports nur nach erfolgreicher Ausgabe.
</de-DE>
<es-419>
El flujo de exportacion fallback ahora es mas confiable cuando falla el anuncio rewarded, con mejor coordinacion del tour y consumo de prueba solo tras salida exitosa.
</es-419>
<fr-FR>
Le flux d export fallback est maintenant plus fiable quand une pub rewarded echoue, avec une meilleure coordination du tour et une consommation d essai seulement apres une sortie reussie.
</fr-FR>
<hi-IN>
Rewarded ad fail hone par fallback export flow ab zyada reliable hai, tour coordination behtar hai, aur trial sirf successful output ke baad consume hota hai.
</hi-IN>
<it-IT>
Il flusso export fallback ora e piu affidabile quando la rewarded ad fallisce, con migliore coordinamento del tour e consumo prova solo dopo output riuscito.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
Rewarded ad no shippai ji ni fallback export flow ga yori antei. Tour no kyouchou ga kaizen sare, trial wa seikou shita output no ato dake shouhi saremasu.
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
Rewarded ad silpae si fallback export flow ga deo anjeongjeogimnida. Tour yeondong i gaeseon doeeotgo, trial eun seonggong output ihueman sojidoemnida.
</ko-KR>
<pt-BR>
O fluxo de exportacao fallback agora esta mais confiavel quando o anuncio rewarded falha, com melhor coordenacao do tour e consumo de teste so apos saida bem sucedida.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
Fallback eksport teper nadezhnee pri sboye rewarded ads, s luchshei koordinatsiei tour i rashodom proby tolko posle uspeshnogo vyvoda.
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
Dang rewarded ad shibai shi, fallback export flow geng wending. Tour xietong geng hao, qie trial zhizai chenggong output hou xiaofei.
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
Dang rewarded ad shibai shi, fallback export flow geng wending. Tour xietong geng hao, qie trial zhizai chenggong output hou xiaofei.
</zh-TW>
