<en-US>
Remove Ads now opens as a full-screen upgrade page, keeps the benefit list compact, and anchors the CTA, one-time purchase copy, and Restore Purchase in the footer.
</en-US>
<ar>
تفتح شاشة Remove Ads الآن كصفحة ترقية بملء الشاشة، وتبقي قائمة المزايا مدمجة، مع تثبيت زر الإجراء ونص الشراء لمرة واحدة وخيار استعادة الشراء في التذييل.
</ar>
<de-DE>
Remove Ads offnet sich jetzt als Vollbild-Upgrade-Seite, halt die Vorteilsliste kompakt und verankert CTA, Einmalkauf-Hinweis und Kaufwiederherstellung im Footer.
</de-DE>
<es-419>
Remove Ads ahora se abre como una pantalla de upgrade a pantalla completa, mantiene compacta la lista de beneficios y deja el CTA, el texto de compra unica y la restauracion de compra anclados en el pie.
</es-419>
<fr-FR>
Remove Ads s'ouvre desormais comme une page d'upgrade plein ecran, garde la liste des avantages compacte et ancre le CTA, le texte d'achat unique et la restauration d'achat dans le pied de page.
</fr-FR>
<hi-IN>
Remove Ads अब एक full-screen upgrade page के रूप में खुलता है, लाभ सूची को compact रखता है, और CTA, one-time purchase टेक्स्ट, तथा restore purchase को footer में स्थिर रखता है.
</hi-IN>
<it-IT>
Remove Ads ora si apre come una pagina di upgrade a schermo intero, mantiene compatta la lista dei vantaggi e ancora CTA, testo di acquisto una tantum e ripristino acquisto nel footer.
</it-IT>
<ja-JP>
Remove Ads は全画面のアップグレードページとして開き、特典リストをコンパクトに保ち、CTA、1回払いの案内、購入の復元をフッターに固定します。
</ja-JP>
<ko-KR>
Remove Ads는 이제 전체 화면 업그레이드 페이지로 열리며, 혜택 목록은 컴팩트하게 유지되고 CTA, 일회성 구매 문구, 구매 복원은 푸터에 고정됩니다.
</ko-KR>
<pt-BR>
Remove Ads agora abre como uma pagina de upgrade em tela cheia, mantem a lista de beneficios compacta e fixa o CTA, o texto de compra unica e a restauracao da compra no rodape.
</pt-BR>
<ru-RU>
Remove Ads теперь открывается как полноэкранная страница апгрейда, держит список преимуществ компактным и закрепляет CTA, текст разовой покупки и восстановление покупки внизу.
</ru-RU>
<zh-CN>
Remove Ads 现在会以全屏升级页打开，保持权益列表紧凑，并将 CTA、一次性购买说明和恢复购买固定在底部。
</zh-CN>
<zh-TW>
Remove Ads 現在會以全螢幕升級頁開啟，讓權益列表保持緊湊，並將 CTA、一次性購買說明和恢復購買固定在底部。
</zh-TW>
