<en-US>
New Image | Scratch source selector added. Scratch now opens editor directly on background tools. Tour flow and thumbnail preview were updated for clearer crop expectations.
</en-US>

<ar>
Tam idafat mukhayyir masdar jadid image | scratch. yabhath scratch alaan al-muharrir mubasharatan ila adawat al-khalfiyah. tam tahdith al-tour wa al-musaghara li idhhar nisbat al-qass biwuduh.
</ar>

<de-DE>
Neue Auswahl Image | Scratch hinzugefuegt. Scratch oeffnet den Editor jetzt direkt bei den Hintergrund-Werkzeugen. Tour-Ablauf und Miniaturvorschau wurden fuer klarere Crop-Erwartung verbessert.
</de-DE>

<es-419>
Se agrego selector de fuente Image | Scratch. Scratch ahora abre el editor directo en herramientas de fondo. Se actualizo el tour y la miniatura para mostrar mejor la expectativa real del recorte.
</es-419>

<fr-FR>
Nouveau selecteur Image | Scratch ajoute. Scratch ouvre maintenant l editeur directement sur les outils de fond. Le tour et la miniature ont ete ajustes pour mieux refleter le recadrage reel.
</fr-FR>

<hi-IN>
Naya Image | Scratch source selector add hua. Scratch ab editor ko seedha background tools par kholta hai. Tour flow aur thumbnail preview ko real crop expectation ke liye update kiya gaya.
</hi-IN>

<it-IT>
Aggiunto nuovo selettore Image | Scratch. Scratch ora apre l editor direttamente sugli strumenti di sfondo. Tour e anteprima miniatura aggiornati per mostrare meglio il ritaglio reale.
</it-IT>

<ja-JP>
Image | Scratch no sentaku o tsuika. Scratch wa haikei tool ni chokusetu hairu editor de hirakimasu. Tour to mini preview o koushin shi, crop no mie kata o wakariyasuku shimashita.
</ja-JP>

<ko-KR>
Image | Scratch soseu seontaegi chuga doeeotseumnida. Scratch-neun ije editor-reul baegyeong tool-eseo jeuksi yeoreumnida. Tour-wa thumb preview-ga silje crop biyul-e match doedorok gaeseon doeeotseumnida.
</ko-KR>

<pt-BR>
Novo seletor de origem Image | Scratch adicionado. Scratch agora abre o editor direto nas ferramentas de fundo. Tour e miniatura foram atualizados para mostrar melhor a expectativa real de corte.
</pt-BR>

<ru-RU>
Dobavlen novyi vybor istochnika Image | Scratch. Rezhim scratch teper otkryvaet redaktor srazu na instrumentakh fona. Tur i miniatyura obnovleny dlya bolee ponyatnogo ozhidaniya crop.
</ru-RU>

<zh-CN>
Yi xin zeng Image | Scratch laiyuan xuanze. Scratch xianzai zhijie jinru bianjiqi de beijing gongju. Tour he suolue tu yijing gengxin, geng qingchu fan ying shiji caijian bili.
</zh-CN>

<zh-TW>
Yi xin zeng Image | Scratch laiyuan xuanze. Scratch xianzai zhijie jinru bianjiqi de beijing gongju. Tour he suolue tu yi gengxin, geng qingchu fanying shiji caijian bili.
</zh-TW>
