<en-US>
Tour alignment is now more stable during warnings, modals, and quick UI changes. Guide now starts the full tour, including editor and remove-ads steps.
</en-US>

<ar>
اصبح محاذاة الجولة اكثر ثباتا اثناء التحذيرات والنوافذ المنبثقة وتغيرات الواجهة السريعة. زر الدليل يبدأ الان الجولة الكاملة بما في ذلك خطوات المحرر وازالة الاعلانات.
</ar>

<de-DE>
Die Tour-Ausrichtung ist jetzt stabiler bei Warnungen, Modalen und schnellen UI-Aenderungen. Guide startet jetzt die komplette Tour inklusive Editor- und Remove-Ads-Schritten.
</de-DE>

<es-419>
El tour ahora se mantiene mejor alineado durante advertencias, modales y cambios rapidos de la interfaz. Guia ahora inicia el tour completo, incluyendo editor y pasos de quitar anuncios.
</es-419>

<fr-FR>
L alignement du tour est maintenant plus stable pendant les alertes, modales et changements rapides de l interface. Guide lance maintenant le tour complet, avec l editeur et les etapes remove ads.
</fr-FR>

<hi-IN>
अब टूर अलाइनमेंट चेतावनियों, मोडल्स और तेज UI बदलावों के दौरान ज्यादा स्थिर है। गाइड अब पूरा टूर शुरू करता है, जिसमें एडिटर और remove ads स्टेप्स शामिल हैं।
</hi-IN>

<it-IT>
L allineamento del tour e ora piu stabile durante avvisi, modali e cambi rapidi dell interfaccia. Guida ora avvia il tour completo, inclusi editor e passaggi remove ads.
</it-IT>

<ja-JP>
警告やモーダル、素早いUI変化の間でも、ツアーの位置合わせがより安定しました。ガイドは編集と広告削除ステップを含むフルツアーを開始します。
</ja-JP>

<ko-KR>
경고, 모달, 빠른 UI 변경 중에도 투어 정렬이 더 안정적으로 동작합니다. 가이드는 이제 에디터와 광고 제거 단계를 포함한 전체 투어를 시작합니다.
</ko-KR>

<pt-BR>
O alinhamento do tour esta mais estavel durante avisos, modais e mudancas rapidas da interface. Guia agora inicia o tour completo, incluindo editor e etapas de remover anuncios.
</pt-BR>

<ru-RU>
Выравнивание тура стало стабильнее при предупреждениях, модальных окнах и быстрых изменениях интерфейса. Кнопка Guide теперь запускает полный тур, включая шаги редактора и удаления рекламы.
</ru-RU>

<zh-CN>
现在在警告、弹窗和快速界面变化时，导览定位更稳定。指南按钮会启动完整导览，包括编辑器和去广告步骤。
</zh-CN>

<zh-TW>
現在在警告、彈窗與快速介面變化時，導覽定位更穩定。指南按鈕會啟動完整導覽，包含編輯器與移除廣告步驟。
</zh-TW>
