<en-US>
EPUB Cover Changer now uses consistent settings buttons for language, theme, privacy, and feedback, with cleaner alignment and no extra checkmark in the simple rows.
</en-US>

<ar>
يستخدم EPUB Cover Changer الآن أزرار إعدادات موحّدة للغة والمظهر والخصوصية والتعليقات، مع محاذاة أنظف ومن دون علامة صح إضافية في الصفوف البسيطة.
</ar>

<de-DE>
EPUB Cover Changer verwendet jetzt einheitliche Einstellungs-Schaltflächen für Sprache, Design, Datenschutz und Feedback, mit saubererer Ausrichtung und ohne zusätzliches Häkchen in den einfachen Zeilen.
</de-DE>

<es-419>
EPUB Cover Changer ahora usa botones de ajustes consistentes para idioma, tema, privacidad y comentarios, con una mejor alineación y sin la marca de selección extra en las filas simples.
</es-419>

<fr-FR>
EPUB Cover Changer utilise maintenant des boutons de réglages cohérents pour la langue, le thème, la confidentialité et les commentaires, avec un alignement plus propre et sans coche supplémentaire dans les lignes simples.
</fr-FR>

<hi-IN>
EPUB Cover Changer अब भाषा, थीम, गोपनीयता और फ़ीडबैक के लिए एकसमान सेटिंग्स बटन इस्तेमाल करता है, बेहतर संरेखण के साथ और सरल पंक्तियों में अतिरिक्त चेकमार्क के बिना।
</hi-IN>

<it-IT>
EPUB Cover Changer ora usa pulsanti impostazioni coerenti per lingua, tema, privacy e feedback, con un allineamento più pulito e senza un segno di spunta extra nelle righe semplici.
</it-IT>

<ja-JP>
EPUB Cover Changer は、言語、テーマ、プライバシー、フィードバックに共通の設定ボタンを使うようになり、配置がより整い、シンプルな行の余分なチェックマークもなくなりました。
</ja-JP>

<ko-KR>
EPUB Cover Changer는 이제 언어, 테마, 개인정보 보호, 피드백에 공통 설정 버튼을 사용하며, 정렬이 더 깔끔해지고 단순한 행의 추가 체크 표시도 사라졌습니다.
</ko-KR>

<pt-BR>
O EPUB Cover Changer agora usa botões de ajustes consistentes para idioma, tema, privacidade e feedback, com alinhamento mais limpo e sem marca de seleção extra nas linhas simples.
</pt-BR>

<ru-RU>
EPUB Cover Changer теперь использует единые кнопки настроек для языка, темы, конфиденциальности и отзывов, с более аккуратным выравниванием и без лишней галочки в простых строках.
</ru-RU>

<zh-CN>
EPUB Cover Changer 现在为语言、主题、隐私和反馈使用统一的设置按钮，布局对齐更整洁，简单选项里也不再多出勾选标记。
</zh-CN>

<zh-TW>
EPUB Cover Changer 現在為語言、主題、隱私和回饋使用統一的設定按鈕，對齊更整潔，簡單選項中也不再多出勾選標記。
</zh-TW>
