<en-US>
Added Image | Scratch source actions. After Done from image or scratch, Best Candidate now hides again. In scratch mode, Same Image stays disabled and Eyedropper unlocks only after choosing a color.
</en-US>

<ar>
Tam idafat image | scratch. baad done min image aw scratch, akhyar murashah yakhfii marra ukhra. fi scratch, same image yabqa muattalan wa eyedropper yatafaal baad ikhtiyar lawn.
</ar>

<de-DE>
Image | Scratch Quelle hinzugefuegt. Nach Done aus Image oder Scratch wird Best Candidate wieder ausgeblendet. Im Scratch-Modus bleibt Same Image deaktiviert und Eyedropper wird erst nach Farbauswahl aktiv.
</de-DE>

<es-419>
Se agregaron acciones de fuente Image | Scratch. Despues de Done desde imagen o scratch, Best Candidate se vuelve a ocultar. En modo scratch, Same Image queda deshabilitado y Eyedropper solo se habilita tras elegir color.
</es-419>

<fr-FR>
Ajout des actions source Image | Scratch. Apres Done depuis image ou scratch, Best Candidate se masque a nouveau. En mode scratch, Same Image reste desactive et Eyedropper s active seulement apres choix d une couleur.
</fr-FR>

<hi-IN>
Image | Scratch source actions add kiye gaye. Image ya scratch se Done ke baad Best Candidate fir hide hota hai. Scratch mode me Same Image disabled rehta hai aur Eyedropper color choose karne ke baad hi enable hota hai.
</hi-IN>

<it-IT>
Aggiunte azioni sorgente Image | Scratch. Dopo Done da image o scratch, Best Candidate torna nascosto. In modalita scratch, Same Image resta disabilitato e Eyedropper si abilita solo dopo scelta colore.
</it-IT>

<ja-JP>
Image | Scratch source action o tsuika. Image matawa scratch kara Done no ato, Best Candidate wa futatabi kakuremasu. Scratch mode dewa Same Image wa muko no mama, Eyedropper wa iro sentaku go ni nomi yuukou.
</ja-JP>

<ko-KR>
Image | Scratch source action-i chuga doeeotseumnida. Image ttoneun scratch-eseo Done hu Best Candidate-neun dasi sumgyeojimnida. Scratch mode-eseo Same Image-neun biyonghwa, Eyedropper-neun saeg sangtae seontaek hu-e man hwalseonghwa doemnida.
</ko-KR>

<pt-BR>
Foram adicionadas acoes de origem Image | Scratch. Depois de Done por imagem ou scratch, Best Candidate volta a ficar oculto. No modo scratch, Same Image continua desabilitado e Eyedropper so ativa apos escolher cor.
</pt-BR>

<ru-RU>
Dobavleny deistviya istochnika Image | Scratch. Posle Done iz image ili scratch Best Candidate snova skryvaetsya. V rezhime scratch Same Image ostayotsya otklyuchen, a Eyedropper vklyuchaetsya tolko posle vybora cveta.
</ru-RU>

<zh-CN>
Yi zengjia Image | Scratch laiyuan anniu. Cong image huo scratch dianji Done hou, Best Candidate hui zai ci yincang. Zai scratch moshi zhong, Same Image baochi jinyong, Eyedropper xuyao xian xuanze yanse cai neng qiyong.
</zh-CN>

<zh-TW>
Yi zengjia Image | Scratch laiyuan anniu. Cong image huo scratch dianji Done hou, Best Candidate hui zai ci yincang. Zai scratch moshi zhong, Same Image baochi jinyong, Eyedropper bixu xian xuanze yanse cai neng qiyong.
</zh-TW>
